elevatedtraffic.com 2018-08-20

# Elevated Traffic

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

Information Collected

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

In order to utilize the services at Elevated traffic, users must register.    
As appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

      • To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
      • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
      • To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

Security  
How do we protect your information?

We take every precaution to protect our members information. The site offers high security SSL login and encryption on ever page where personal details are added. Only the administrator of this website has access to members email address and other information. We do NOT sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

All financial transactions are processed through a payment gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

Information Updates

At any time, user may access their personal members area and update their accont profile.  

Members Right to Cancel  
At any time a member can request to have their account deleted from "the site" by clicking "Delete Account" in the member's profile or submitting a support ticket with the request.  At that time, the account will be permanently removed from the database.

Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:  
      Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
      Identify the pages being used to better analyze data and improve the overall performance of our website.

Once data is reviewed, it is removed from our system.  We do not gain access to your computer or private information, other than the data you share with us.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If users disable cookies in their browser:

If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features available within the member's area.

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third-party links  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, "the site" cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?  
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 18 years old.  We do not collect data from minors knowlingly.  If such information is discovered, it will be immediately deleted

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify you via email  
      • Within 7 business days

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:  
      Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions  
      Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:  
      Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
      Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
      Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
      Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
      Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
      Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails:  
      • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.  
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

Policy Change Notification

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Beth Allen  
6969 Brian Crescent  
Niagara Falls, ON L2J3P5  
Canada  
admin@elevatedtraffic.com

Copyright © 2009 - 2018. Elevated Traffic. All rights reserved.
